[
  {
    "front": "학교",
    "back": "School"
  },
  {
    "front": "담장",
    "back": "Fence"
  },
  {
    "front": "놀이터",
    "back": "Playground"
  },
  {
    "front": "사람들",
    "back": "People"
  },
  {
    "front": "알다",
    "back": "Know"
  },
 {
    "front": "새/새로운",
    "back": "New"
  },
  {
    "front": "흥분한/신난",
    "back": "Excited"
  },
  {
    "front": "굴착기",
    "back": "Digger"
  },
  {
    "front": "교실",
    "back": "Classroom"
  },
  {
    "front": "사진",
    "back": "Photograph"
  },
  {
    "front": "블록",
    "back": "Block"
  },
  {
    "front": "기다리다",
    "back": "Wait"
  },
  {
    "front": "기중기",
    "back": "Crane"
  },
  {
    "front": "떨어뜨리다",
    "back": "Drop"
  },
  {
    "front": "잘못된",
    "back": "Wrong"
  },
  {
    "front": "뒤집힌",
    "back": "Upside down"
  },
  {
    "front": "듣다",
    "back": "Listen"
  },
  {
    "front": "안쪽",
    "back": "Inside"
  },
  {
    "front": "놀라다",
    "back": "Gasp"
  }
]